本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》  前情提要
Previously on 24
我哥哥情况如何
I need to know about my brother.
他还活着  快跑吧
He's alive. Get out now.
他们很快就会意识到你就是幕后黑手了
It can't be long before they realize it's you.
您快点回车里去
I need you to get back in the car.
您的弟弟参与策划了这次炸弹袭击
Your brother was involved with the attack.
他就是我们一直在找的内应
He's the insider we've been looking for.
怎么回事
What's going on?
尸体触发了危险物警报
The body triggered a Hazmat alarm.
是高浓缩铀
It's highly enriched uranium.
你的意思是它属于武器级别吗
You mean it's weapons-grade?
他到底怎么会接触到这种物质的
How the hell did he come into contact with that?
我想我知道怎么回事
I think I know the answer.
有个持有武器级浓缩铀的人去找过我弟弟
Someone approached my brother with weapons-grade uranium.
-谁  -此人能接触到前苏联废弃的核原料堆
- Who? - Someone who had access to decommissioned Soviet stockpile.
你必须要在俄罗斯人把铀给我弟弟前找到他们
You must find the Russians before they can get the uranium to my brother.
我要看你手里有浓缩铀棒的证据
I want proof that the rods exist,
不然你休想得到钱
or you will not be paid.
你要证据是吧
You want proof, huh?
跟我来
Come with me.
我的小儿子
My younger son,
他负责运输浓缩铀棒
he was transporting the rods,
但他太大意了
and he was careless.
看到了吧  这就是你要的证据了
There, you have your proof.
你在俄罗斯黑帮中做了近两年的卧底
You were undercover for nearly two years with the Russian mob.
你的身份并未被揭穿
Your cover is still intact.
你的意思是让我打回内部去吗
Are you asking me to go back in?
沃克探员结束卧底工作已经六年多了
Agent Walker hasn't been undercover for over six years.
我认为不应该让她来执行这个任务
I think you're making a mistake by putting her in.
你一定还有其他选择
You must have other options.
她是我们打入敌人内部的唯一途径
She's our only way in.
那好  我跟她一起去
Fine, then I want to go with her.
我猜你的计划是找人假扮成竞价的买主
I assume your plan is trying to set up a competing buy?
就由我来假扮买主好了
I'll act as a buyer.
我在找瓦德米尔
I'm looking for Vladimir.
瓦德失踪了
Vlad disappeared.
但你能找到他
But you can find him.
他们每时每刻都知道我在哪儿
They know where I am 24/7.
我和在监狱没什么两样
I'm still in prison.
假释期的追踪器
Parole bracelet?
我能把这玩意拿下来
I can get this off.
你不能割断追踪器
You can't cut bracelet.
我也没打算那样做
I'm not gonna cut the bracelet.
看你都干了些什么
What the hell have you done?!
够了  到此为止吧
That's it, this is over.
杰克  对你来说结束了  而我才刚开始
Maybe for you, Jack, but I'm just getting started.
以下事件发生于晚上八点到九点
The following takes place between 8:00 P.M. and 9:00 P.M.
卡米斯坦伊斯兰共和国
今天的首都  忠于哈桑总统的军队
抓捕了很多意图颠覆政权的叛徒
政府的各个部门中都揪出了嫌犯
我还以为你不是死了就是给抓了呢
I thought you were dead or captured.
我好不容易才摆脱他们的追捕
It took me this long to get clear.
我和巴扎耶夫在一起
I'm with Bazhaev.
去他妈的巴扎耶夫
To hell with Bazhaev!
都是因为他  我们的努力才付之东流
Everything we have worked for, it's all over because of him.
你这就言之过早了  将军
It's not over, General.
当然都玩完了
Of course it is!
你的哥哥还活着
Your brother is still alive,
你的元首梦也破碎了
and your plan to replace him as head of state is finished.
现在他的卫队正全城搜捕我们
Now his security forces are rounding up our people all over the city.
就在五分钟前  阿米礼将军
General Amiri was just pulled from his home five minutes ago,
在家人面前被逮捕了
in front of his wife and children.
美国人不会同意他这样继续下去
Look, the Americans won't let him continue.
会指责他侵犯了人权
They'll accuse him of human rights violations
并以退出和平会谈为威胁
and threaten to pull out of the peace talks.
等浓缩铀一到手
Once we have the uranium,
我哥哥就不再是问题了
my brother will become irrelevant anyway.
你被人四处追捕
You are being hunted like an animal.
怎么把浓缩铀拿到手
How do you expect to get the uranium?
巴扎耶夫可以帮我们拿到手
Bazhaev can deliver it to us,
但我需要先把钱打到他的账户上
but first I need payment wired to his account.
没事的
It's all right.
谢谢
Mm. Thank you.
翻译：aiai    techioo    hodala    ETSChina    淑珍
■
时间轴：何何    卓卓    冰卡      校对：何何   Nil  aiai   冰卡
后期：冰河     监制：何何   冰卡
■
爸爸  弗农山有个诊所
Papa, there's a clinic in Mt. Vernon.
我在那边找到了一个能治疗他的医生
I found a doctor who can treat him.
我们不是说好了吗
We have been through this.
不找医生
No doctors.
没错  但是这个医生有家小
Yes, but this one has a family.
我知道他们的名字和住址
I know where they are, I know their names.
我保证让他守口如瓶
I'll make sure he keeps his mouth shut.
你也能保证诊所里其他人不会发现吗
And you can guarantee no one else in this clinic will find out?
保证别的医生  护士  任何人不泄密吗
Another doctor, a nurse, no one?
当局知道核原料的事情
The authorities know about the nuclear material
或者不久就会知道了
or they will soon enough,
他们会四处查找的
and they'll be looking everywhere.
把欧力格送医会引狼入室
Putting Oleg in a clinic would lead them right to us.
如果我们不赶紧把他送医的话他会死的
He's going to die if we don't get him help.
那让他死好了
Then he's going to die.
但让他如此孤单地死在
But alone like this?
厨房后面冰冷的屋子里吗
In a cold room behind the kitchen?
他是我的弟弟  爸爸
He's my brother, Papa,
也是您的儿子啊
and he's your son.
好吧
All right.
把他带去郊区别墅
Take him to the country house.
乌兰娜会照顾他的
Ulana will look after him.
谢谢  爸爸
Thank you, Papa.
什么事
What is it?
法哈德找你
Farhad is asking for you.
有新消息吗
You have news for me?
是的
Yes.
钱马上就汇到你的账户了
The money will be transferred to your account shortly.
什么时候给我浓缩铀棒
When can I take possession of the rods?
钱一到就给你
As soon as we have the money.
给我五个小时
Five hours.
很好
Good.
我帮你打发时间吧
I'll help you pass the time.
有特殊偏好吗
You have a preference?
没
No.
那两个都归你吧
Then take both.
他还在出血
He's still bleeding out.
这个应该可以止血的
This should cauterize the wound.
好了
Okay, it's working.
你打给谁
Who are you calling?
-黑斯廷斯  -为什么
- Hastings. - Why?
我要让他取消这次行动
Because I'm shutting this operation down.
你还没准备好出外勤  这就是证据
You shouldn't be in the field, and this proves it.
只能赌上这一把了  杰克
This was the only play, Jack.
换你也会这么做的
You would've done the same thing.
放手一搏的目的是让他合作
The play was to get him to cooperate.
-他会合作的  -你怎么知道
- He will cooperate. - How do you figure?
我了解这帮人  杰克
Look, I know these guys, Jack.
兹亚除了幼女之外  最爱的就是钱了
The only thing that Ziya likes more than 13-year-old girls is money.
让他赚这么一大笔  他死都愿意
He'd have butchered himself for a score like this.
是啊  但黑斯廷斯仍需要知道真相
Yeah, well, Hastings still needs to know the truth.
就是你状态一点也不稳定
That you're unstable!
听着  我不怪你
Look... I don't blame you
毕竟你经历了这么多坎坷
after everything you've been through,
但是你不适合这个任务
but you are not fit for this mission.
我的确有过一段艰辛坎坷的日子
I went through a rough patch, yeah,
但我从低谷中走了出来
but I came out on the other side.
我可不这么认为
And I don't think you have.
不管怎么说
The bottom line is,
我还是帮你们夺取浓缩铀的最佳人选
I'm still the best chance that anyone has of intercepting that uranium,
我现在就能做到
and I can do it now.
现在怎样  你还打电话吗
So, what's it going to be, you making that phone call or what?
他快醒了  杰克
He's waking up, Jack.
赶紧决定吧
Better make up your mind.
好吧
Fine.
看你能问出什么来
You see what you can get out of him.
但别忘了  我都听得见
But don't forget, I'm listening.
闭嘴  兹亚
Shut up, Ziya.
我们一出去就给你止痛药
You'll get your painkillers as soon as we get out of here.
-你都做了些什么  -我帮你拿下了追踪器
- What did you do?! - I got the bracelet off,
帮了你一个忙啊
all right, I did you a favor.
你这个疯婊子  把我拇指切掉了
You crazy bitch! You cut off thumb!
木已成舟
Look, what's done is done.
要么你在这像婴儿一样哭嚎抱怨
You can either stay here and whine about it like a baby,
要么你跟我来大赚一笔
or you can come with me and be a rich man.
我可以从总收入里给你分成
Look, I'm willing to give you a point on this deal off the top.
是很大的一笔钱啊  兹亚
It's a lot of money, Ziya.
多少
How much?
250万
Two-and-a-half million.
事成后  300万也说不定
Maybe three when it's all done.
200万
Two million?
真的吗
You're serious?
你说呢
You tell me.
我把这笔买卖介绍给瓦德米尔
I take this deal to Vladimir,
如果是骗局  你知道后果吗
and it's not real, you know what happens?!
如果是骗局我又何必过来
Why would I be here if this wasn't real?!
算了  兹亚
Fine, forget it, Ziya.
我会自己找到瓦德米尔的
I'll find Vladimir my own way.
不  等等
No, wait!
我不知道他的确切位置
I don't know where he is exactly,
不过知道他可能去哪
but where he might be.
说
Tell me.
现在不是时候  我一会儿带你去
No, I'll take you there myself.
你有车吗
You have a car?
我有辆货车  停在后面
I have truck; it's parked out back.
好吧  我来开
All right, I'll drive.
起来
Come on!
喂
Yeah?
杰克  我刚刚在背景资料里发现
Jack, I just found out in my background check
兹亚还有个假释官
that Ziya has a probation officer.
-你要怎么处理  -没必要管了
- How do you want to handle this? - You don't need to.
他还戴着假释期追踪器
He has a tracking bracelet.
现在没了
Not anymore.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这东西有反干预系统
Those things have anti-tamper mechanisms.
你们不可能取下它而不触动警报
You can't cut them off him without triggering an alarm.
是  但相信我  已经处理好了
Yeah, well, trust me, it's been taken care of.
杰克  那儿发生了什么
Jack, what happened in there?
蕾妮得到她想要的结果了
Renee got the result she wanted.
兹亚会带她去瓦德米尔那里
Ziya's taking her to Vladimir.
丹娜还在伪造你的档案
Dana's still working on your cover profile.
好了  他们走了
Okay, they're moving.
档案好了我给你电话
I'll call you when it's ready.
杰克还在等剩下部分的档案
Jack's still waiting on the rest of that profile.
我还在处理时间表  告诉他我快好了
I'm still working the timeline. Tell him I'm almost finished.
好的
Okay.
家中来电
Home
你不接吗
Aren't you going to get that?
是  我正准备接
Yeah, probably should.
喂
Hello?
我在忙
I'm in the middle of something.
稍等
Hold on a second.
克罗伊  我尽快传给你那个档案
Chloe, I will send that profile to you as soon as I'm done.
好的
Okay.
我告诉过你别再打过来
I told you not to call.
是  我知道你告诉过我
Yeah, I know what you told me.
但由于我身在你的公寓里的缘故
But now that I'm here in your apartment,
我就是情不自禁地想你
I just can't help but miss you.
我到早上就下班了  到时候我去见你
My shift is over in the morning. I will see you then.
那不行  现在就来
Yeah, well, that's just not going to work now, is it?
我现在很忙  卡文
I'm right in the middle of something, Kevin.
你要是不相信我就看看新闻
Turn on the news if you don't believe me.
那不关我的事
Hey, that's not my problem.
我要见你
Okay, I need to see you.
-给你十五分钟  -这不可能啊
- You have 15 minutes. - That's not possible.
好吧  那就三十分钟
Okay, you got 30.
谁说我不通情达理来着
Who said I can't be reasonable?
卡文
Kevin...
别逼我打给你的小男友
Don't make me call that little boyfriend of yours.
让他美好的生活见鬼去吧
Rock his perfect little world.
老兄  恭喜你订婚了
"Hey, pal, congratulations on the engagement."
顺便说下  她不叫丹娜·沃什
"By the way, her name's not Dana Walsh,"
而是珍妮·斯科特
"it's Jenny Scott."
对了  我说过她有前科吗
"Oh, did I mention that she's an ex-con?"
不  不  没什么大不了
"No, no, no, nothing too serious."
只是个谋杀犯的同伙而已啦
"Just accessory to murder is all."
你还在吗
You still there?
是的
Yeah, I'm here.
待会见
See you soon.
阿洛  能求你点事吗
Arlo, can I ask you something?
问吧  星期六晚上我有空
Yes, I'm available Saturday night,
如果你有需要  我周五也行
and I can change my plans for Friday if you want.
或者星期四也有空
Also, I'm free on Thursday.
抱歉  阿洛
Look, Arlo, I'm sorry.
我家里刚刚有点事
It's just, a situation's come up,
所以我得回家一趟
and I have to go home for a while.
丹娜  我们现在正处于非常时期
Dana, we're in the middle of a major protocol.
我知道  但是我保证不会去太久
I understand that, and I won't be long, I promise.
但需要你帮我做下我的工作
But I need you to cover for me.
完成蕾妮·沃克和杰克·鲍尔的卧底档案
Put the finishing touches on the profile for Renee Walker and Jack Bauer.
如果我问你回去干什么  你会说
And if I ask what this is about, you'll tell me...
-这不关你的事  -一我想也是
- That it's none of your business. - Right. I thought so.
你尽快完成然后传给克罗伊
Send it to Chloe's screen as soon as you're finished.
好
Okay.
谢谢  阿洛  算我欠你一次
Thank you, Arlo. I owe you one.
一次什么
One what?
谢谢  总理先生
Thank you, Mr. Prime Minister.
期待明天和您的会面
I look forward to seeing you tomorrow.
我和十二国首脑谈过了
I've spoken to 12 heads of state.
他们有些担心
They're concerned,
不过还是准备参加明天的签字仪式
But they're all still planning to attend the signing ceremony tomorrow.
我有一个坏消息
Well, I've got some bad news.
很明显  刺杀哈桑总统只是
Apparently, killing president Hassan
他弟弟计划的一部分
was only part of his brother's plan.
反恐小组现在可以肯定
CTU now believes
他现在还在试图弄到武器级别的铀
he's also trying to acquire weapons-grade uranium.
从谁手里得到
From whom?
一个在纽约的俄罗斯犯罪团伙
A Russian crime syndicate here in New York.
一半的人都属前苏联军人或是克格勃间谍
Half of them are ex-Soviet Army or KGB.
如果有任何人能弄到极度危险的核原料堆
If anyone had access to unsecured stockpiles...
自冷战以后  我们就一直忧心忡忡
It's what we've been afraid of since the Wall came down.
哈桑总统知道这事吗
Is President Hassan aware of this?
就是他告诉反恐小组的
He's the one who told CTU about it.
黑斯廷斯已展开一次卧底计划
Director Hastings has already initiated an undercover operation
在其走私到其他国家前夺回浓缩铀
to try to recover the uranium before it's smuggled out of the country.
核原料现在就在美国本土吗
The nuclear materials are here on U.S. Soil?
-他们确定吗  -恐怕是的
- Are they sure? - Afraid so.
伊桑  你为什么问哈森总统是否知情
Ethan, you asked if President Hassan was aware of this. Why?
这就解释了伊斯兰共和国的现状了
Helps explain what's been going on in the Islamic Republic.
我刚和驻伊斯兰共和国的大使谈过
I just spoke with our ambassador in the I.R.K.
哈桑的卫队正横扫首都
Hassan's security forces are sweeping through the capital,
逮捕反对党领导人 关闭新闻机构
arresting opposition leaders, shuttering news organizations.
他宣布全城戒严了吗
Has he declared martial law?
官方虽未宣布  但是实际上已经在做了
Not officially, but effectively, that's exactly what he's been doing.
这也怪不得他
Who can blame him?
我是说  他的弟弟肯定还有同伙的
I mean, his brother can't have been acting alone.
我们希望哈桑镇压他政府内的死硬派
We want Hassan cracking down on hardliners in his own government.
但现在他是公然挑衅国家法律
Except that he's defying his country's laws,
以及国际人权公约啊
as well as his international human rights obligations.
如果他继续的话  会威胁到和平公约的合法性
And if he continues, it may delegitimize the peace accord.
哈桑总统从反恐小组回来了吗
Is President Hassan back yet from CTU?
十分钟之后到
He'll be here in ten minutes.
我要单独和他谈谈
I want to speak to him... alone.
我来安排
I'll take care of it.
够了
That's enough.
你怎么管那么多
What's your problem?
我要你头脑清醒
I need you thinking clearly.
你说过要给我止痛药的
You tell me you'd get me real painkiller.
把酒收起来
Put it away.
我很惊讶
I'm surprised.
他那样对待你之后  你还给他介绍买卖
I'm surprised you take deal to him again after what he did to you.
还有多远
How much further?
好
Okay.
你不愿意谈瓦德米尔
You don't want to talk about Vladimir.
我理解  不怪你
I understand. I don't blame you.
毕竟  这样一个男人还有什么好说的
After all, what is there to say about such a man?
没有好事  没有...
Nothing good, nothing very...
你赶紧告诉我
Just tell me
还有多远
how much further.
十分钟
Ten minute.
真开不起玩笑
Touchy, touchy.
喂
Yeah?
阿洛刚把你俩伪装身份的档案关联好了
Arlo just locked your cover profile.
我现在传给你
I'm uplinking it to you now.
好  稍等
Okay, hold on one sec.
好了  我收到了
Okay, I got it.
我们通话时蕾妮听不到的  对吗
Hey, you're taking me out of Renee's comm when you call, right?
对
Yes.
好  我要你进入她和瓦德米尔
Okay, I want you to go into her undercover file
有关联的卧底档案
with regards to Vladimir Laitanan.
我要搞清他们之间发生过的一切
I need to know everything that happened between them.
我稍后给你回复
I'll call you right back.
好  多谢
Okay, thanks.
总统阁下
Mr. President.
您的参谋长跟我说情况紧急
Your chief of staff said it was urgent.
确实如此  但首先
It is, but first,
我想再次表达对您能安然无恙而甚感欣慰
I want to say again how thankful we are that you're all right.
您若是指关于我的卫队
If this is about my security forces
以及我在我国所采取的必要手段的话
and the necessary steps I'm taking back home,
那就恕难从命了
I'm afraid I can't help you.
您真有那个必要采取如此手段吗
Are you so sure they're necessary?
今天所发生的一切不亚于一次政变
What happened today was nothing short of a coup.
就是这同一批家伙
These same people
企图重新启动我国的核武器计划
are trying to restart my country's nuclear weapons' program.
我明白  但是...
I understand, but...
不  我认为你不明白
No, I don't think you do.
贵国是一个开放社会  总统阁下
Yours is an open society, Madam President,
一个法治的国度
governed by the rule of law.
我的国家却很闭塞
Mine is closed.
那里真正的法律便是强权
The only real law is power.
对我而言  若有半点软弱可欺就必死无疑
Any perceived weakness on my part, and I'm finished.
我明白您所处的复杂处境  总统阁下
I'm aware of the complexities of your situation, Mr. President.
我兄弟想置我于死地
My brother tried to kill me,
而帮凶竟然是我自己的手下
helped by elements within my own government.
我必须清理门户
Those elements must now be purged.
清理门户
Purged?
你是说  处决吗
You mean, executed?
这是唯一能让我的子民开窍的方式
It is the only thing my people understand.
总统阁下  如果你违背自己的人权宣言
I can't vouch for you as a reformer, Mr. President,
我是不能对你担保的
if you renege on your human rights obligations.
全世界都相信你是因为我相信你
The world is trusting you because I trust you.
你要我宽恕我的敌人
You're asking me to show mercy to enemies
而那些人却想毁了我
who are trying to destroy me.
我是让你以帮一个祖祖辈辈
I am asking you to find a middle way,
不知和平为何物的国度带去和平为名
in the name of bringing peace to a region
开辟出一条折中的道路
that hasn't known peace for generations.
我现在要去见我的家人了
I need to see my family now.
我找到位医生
I found a doctor.
什么医生
A doctor?
一个受控于我又可以医治你的人
Someone who can help you, someone we can control,
但爸爸说这太冒险了
but Papa says it's too risky.
爸爸是对的
Papa's right.
让你自生自灭也是对的吗
Condemning you to death?
我可不这么想
I don't believe that.
一切... 都是我咎由自取
What happened... was my own fault.
别因为我的失误而拖累整个家庭
The family shouldn't have to pay for my mistake.
知道吗  这些年来我觉得人生如戏
You know, all these years, I thought it was an act.
但你的确是好样的  对吗
But you really are the good son, aren't you?
我和你相差无几  约瑟夫
I'm no better or worse than you, Josef.
你是我大哥
You're my older brother.
你总是很照顾我
You've always looked out for me.
约瑟夫  约瑟夫  你想干嘛
Joseph? Joseph, what are you doing?!
我要带你去看医生
I'm taking you to the doctor.
但爸爸说我们不能去就医
But Papa said we can't.
我才不管爸爸说过什么
I don't care what Papa said!
我不会让你毫无抗争就这么死去
I'm not letting you die without a fight.
你长大了  可以自己拿主意了
You are old enough to make your own decisions.
我决定留下
I've decided to stay.
随你所愿吧
As you wish.
你也应该留下来
You should stay, too.
我不能
I can't.
为什么不
Why not?
你对你父亲的看法只是单方面的
You think that your father is one way,
但是他不是你想的那样
but he's not what you think.
别那么说
Stop doing that.
-你总是那么说  -什么
- You always do that. - What?
含沙射影  但你从不告诉我你的真实想法
Imply things, but you never actually tell me what you mean.
那样做是有好处的  相信我  凯拉
It is better that way, Kayla believe me.
我不想怂恿你和你父亲作对
I don't want to poison you against your father.
看  你又来了
There. You're doing it again.
你连自己的毛病都改不了
You can't help yourself.
什么又来了
Doing what again?
爸爸
Father!
你没事吧
Oh, are you all right?
我们以为...
We thought that...
知道  我知道
I know, I know.
凯拉  我要跟你母亲单独谈谈
Kayla, I need to speak to your mother now alone.
好
Okay.
-达莉亚  -我们没什么好谈的
- Dalia? - We have nothing to say to each other.
你爱她吗
Do you love her?
都结束了
It's over.
我跟她已经说清楚了
I ended it.
你还没回答我的问题
You didn't answer the question.
说实话吧  哪怕就一次
Be honest for once.
给我一点尊重
Show me a little respect.
我是你的妻子  该死
I'm your wife, damn it.
你爱她吗
Do you love her?
或许  我想我爱过她
Maybe I thought I did.
那就坦白吧
Then say it.
现在说这个还有什么意义
What does it matter now?
对我来说有意义
It matters to me.
真相是...
The truth is...
我只是很高兴我还能有那种感觉
...I'm just glad I could still feel something, anything.
难道是我的错  你居然敢那么认为
And that's my fault somehow? How dare you!
我们都有错
Our fault.
互相指责得也够多了
There's enough blame to go around.
达莉亚  求你别走
Dalia, please don't go.
-什么  -我不想让你离开我
- What? - I don't want you to leave.
别担心
Don't worry.
我不会大吵大闹的
I won't make a scene.
这件事后你应该更了解我才对
You should know me better than that by now.
我弟弟是个叛徒
My brother's a traitor.
身为我手下的最高官员居然密谋推翻我
My highest officers are conspiring against me.
而现在泰勒总统居然也威胁我要退出和平会谈
And now President Taylor is threatening to pull out of the peace talks.
你已经很久没向我征询意见了
It has been a long time since you've asked my advice about anything.
你总能给我最好的建议
You were the one who always gave me the best counsel.
谢谢你还能记得这点
Thank you for remembering that.
那你会留下吗
Then you'll stay?
太晚了  奥马
It's too late for that, Omar.
我们之间发生了太多的事
Too much has happened between us.
-达莉亚  -我很遗憾
- Dalia... - I'm sorry.
-瓦德在这活动吗  -有时会
- Vlad operates out of here? - Sometimes.
他总是打一枪换一个地方
He moved around a lot.
这就是条子在这总找不到他的原因
That's why cops don't find him inside here.
快点  我们走
Come on, let's go.
兹亚
Hey, Ziya?
你知道  瓦德米尔从不喜欢惊喜
You know, Vladimi was never fond of surprises,
所以我想
so I was thinking...
应该让你先进去
maybe you could go in first?
让他见我时心里有所准备
Get him used to the idea of me again.
先吊他的胃口吗
Whet his appetite?
-很对  -好的
- Exactly. - Okay.
我俩的伪造档案到位了吗
Is our cover in place?
到位了  克罗伊全搞定了
Yeah. Chloe got me everything.
好  我们开始温习墨西哥城的伪造经历吧
Good. Let's start going over what happened in Mexico City.
我们怎么遇见的  我们的交易对象是谁
How we met, who we dealt with.
先告诉我一些瓦德米尔的事
First tell me about Vladimir.
你想要知道些什么
What do you want to know?
他对你做过什么  我听见兹亚说的了
What he did to you? I heard what Ziya said.
兹亚
Ziya?
得了吧  杰克  他不过是小题大做罢了
Come on, Jack, he's a drama queen.
该死  蕾妮  这次任务我负责
Damn it, Renee, I am running this!
别再跟我兜圈子了
Stop messing with me!
我负责你的安全
I'm responsible for your safety.
所以我问什么
So, when I ask you a straight question,
你就答什么
you give me a straight answer.
听着  什么也没有  行了吧
Look, it was nothing, all right?
六年前我就搞定过他  现在也一样
I handled him six years ago, I can handle him today.
我只担心一件事
The only thing that I am worried about
巩固我们之间的伪造身份  所以  拜托你
is locking down this cover, so, please,
别再在瓦德米尔身上浪费时间了
let's not waste another minute on Vladimir.
我叫恩斯特·迈尔  是慕尼黑的军火商人
I'm a Munich-based arms dealer named Ernst Meier.
我们在墨西哥城结识
We met in Mexico City.
你是我和当地人之间的联络人
You became my liaison to the locals.
好久不见
Long time.
是我啊  兹亚
It's me, Ziya.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你他妈的来这里做什么
Now what the hell are you doing here?
谈生意
I've got business.
-什么生意  -是的
- Business? - Yeah.
和瓦德米尔谈
With Vladimir.
你要和我谈生意吗
You've got business with me?
瓦德
Vlad!
单凭你想来这里这一点  我就该宰了你
I should kill you for even thinking of coming here.
什么
What?
放过我吧  求你了
Let me go, please!
-不  我...  -五年了
- No, I... - Five years
我一直生活在地下
I've been living underground.
五年了  你现在来和我谈生意
Five years! And now you walk into my place of business?
你还在假释期间
You're on probation!
不  不再是了  瓦德
No. Not anymore, Vlad.
看
Look.
是她帮我拿掉追踪器的
She get bracelet off.
你说什么  谁干的
What are you talking about? Who did?
这就是我想告诉你的  是蕾妮
It's what I'm trying to tell you. Renee.
蕾妮·扎丹
Renee Zadan.
她到我那里去找你
She come to my place looking for you.
还有她说  她有个买家
Yeah, she say she have buyer
一个你会有兴趣的买家
that you'd want to hear about.
而且这生意对我们都有好处
That it'd be good for all of us.
有百利而无一害
It'd be worth it for all of us.
蕾妮
Renee.
是的
Dah.
她有说五年来她都在哪吗
She say where she'd been these last five years?
她和其他人一样
Uh, where everybody else was.
在蹲监狱
In jail.
之后她去了墨西哥城
Then she go to Mexico City.
她说在那里逮到机会
She say she got the opportunity there.
墨西哥城吗
Mexico City, huh?
是的  你怎么想的  卢戈
Dah. What do you think, Lugo?
你相信这垃圾的鬼话吗
You believe this piece of dirt?
我当然相信他
Sure I believe him.
他这种蠢货怎么编得出这种故事
He's too stupid to make up a story like that.
但我不太相信她
It's her I don't believe.
应该说我从没信过她
I never did.
我告诉过你  卢戈  不会是她
I told you, Lugo, it wasn't her.
她不是那种会出卖我们的人
She's not the one who sold us out.
她莫名其妙地出现在我们面前
She shows up out of the blue,
16个月后  我们遭遇联邦探员的严打
then 16 months later, the feds are down our throats.
我只是说说而已  瓦德
I'm just saying, Vlad.
你只是说说
You were just saying.
-蕾妮在哪  -在外面
- Where's Renee now? - Outside.
把脸擦干净  带她来见我
Clean yourself up. Bring her to me.
阿洛  丹娜人呢
Arlo, where's Dana?
-她不在她的办公桌前  -她回家了
- She isn't at her desk. - She went home.
回家了
Home?
对
Yeah.
是谁
Who is it?
是我
It's me.
你把我钥匙拿去了
You have my key.
百忙之中还抽空来看我
Nice of you to drop by.
这不好笑
It's not funny.
你搞什么  他是谁
What the hell?! Who's he?
是我博蒙镇的哥们
It's a buddy of mine from Beaumont.
让他滚出去
Get him the hell out of here.
你知道我不能这么做  珍妮
You know I can't do that, Jen.
我已经答应他可以让他留下了
I already told him he could stay.
再赶他走就太不礼貌了
It'd be impolite.
拿着
Here.
这是什么
What's this?
这里有五百块
It's $500.
这是我能从提款机里提取的全部现金了
It's all I could get out of the cash machine.
明天早上再给你另外五百块
I'll get you another 500 in the morning.
你觉得就你聪明
You think you're smart,
其他人都是傻子是吧
and the whole world's stupid.
你想就这么算了可不行  珍妮
That's just not how it is, Jen.
我没觉得你是傻子
I don't think you're stupid.
没有吗  那你怎么还想用一千块把我打发走
No? But you think you can buy me off with $1,000?
我没说把你打发走
I'm not trying to buy you off.
别这样
No, no.
你到底想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
你知道我想要什么吗
You know what I want?
我真正想要的
What I really want
就是你别再像对待白痴一样对我
is for you to stop treating me like some dumbass,
当我是才19岁的飞车党小毛贼吗
19-year-old stickup artist with a fast car!
别以为就你长大了
You're not the only one who's grown up.
别冲动  卡文
Easy, Kevin, easy.
我等这一刻很久了
I've been waiting for this moment.
做梦都在想着
Dreaming about it.
这是你欠我的
You owe me.
如果你觉得是我出庭作证告发你的  我没有
If you think that I testified against you, I didn't.
别对我撒谎
Don't lie to me!
我没撒谎
I'm not lying to you!
我确实比你早出狱
I got out of jail before you did,
但仅仅是因为我犯案时还未成年
yeah, but only because I went in as a minor.
而不是其他的原因
No other reason.
事实上
The truth is,
说什么也无济于事
it doesn't change things,
无论什么理由
one way or another.
我已经调查过你了
See, I've done my homework.
我知道你是干什么工作的
I know what your job is.
我是数据分析师  仅此而已
I'm a data analyst, nothing more.
对  但你是反恐小组的数据分析师
Yeah, but you're a data analyst for CTU.
你有渠道可以搞到很多好东西
You got access to all sorts of good stuff--
比如银行密码啊  港务局货单什么的
bank codes, port authority manifests,
还有股票交易什么的
stock exchange.
我是有渠道  但不是所有的渠道
Access, yeah, but not unrestricted access.
你会想办法搞到的
You'll figure something out.
你总会有办法的
You always do.
我不管你给我什么
But whatever it is,
但必须得值至少六位数  懂了吗
the payout's got to be at least six figures, okay?
求你了  卡文
Please, Kevin.
好吧  听好了
Okay, here's the deal.
你只帮我这一次
You do this one thing for me,
我就立马消失
and I'm gone.
两不相欠  再也不来打扰你
I'll never bother you again.
我办不到
I can't.
你当然能
You can.
而且你肯定能
And you will.
从去年八月起  我们一直活动并下榻于
Since last August, we've been living and operating out of a hotel
亚文尼达·华雷斯大道上的贝拉诺谢酒店
called Bella Noche on Avenida Juarez.
那是一家专门为高端犯罪提供庇护场所的酒店
Yeah, it's been set up as a safe haven for high-end criminal activity.
不会留记录的  名字记住了吗
They don't keep records. Have you got the name?
贝拉诺谢酒店  记住了
Bella Noche. I got it.
好  我会一直监听  边听边告诉你细节
Okay, I'm going to be monitoring you, filling in the details.
听好我说的就行
Just listen to my voice.
我会告诉你所有需要的信息
I'll get you all the information you need.
他来了
He's coming.
下车  我们走
Come on. Let's go.
说
Yeah?
事情可不太妙  杰克
It's not pretty, Jack.
她的问题很严重
She had a real problem on her hands.
说来听听
Talk to me.
据负责她案子的探员所讲
According to the responsible agent,
瓦德米尔·勒塔纳对她极度着迷
Vladimir Laitanan was completely obsessed with her.
以至于举止粗暴
It turned violent.
有多粗暴
How violent?
肋骨骨折  颧骨骨裂
Broken ribs, a busted cheekbone.
被送去过几次急诊室
A couple of trips to the emergency room.
他有强奸她吗
Did he rape her?
档案上没说
Not according to these files,
但看起来他至少曾几次试图强奸她
but it looks like he tried a couple of times.
她有告诉你或者黑斯廷斯这些没
Did she say anything about this to you or Hastings?
没有
No.
怎么了  杰克
What's this about, Jack?
杰克
Jack?
联调局竭尽所能地掩盖了这些事
The FBI tried to cover this up as much as they could.
但自从她离开了联调局以后
But after she left the bureau,
蕾妮日渐消沉
Renee went into a tailspin.
就我所知  她至少试图自杀过一次
She tried to kill herself at least once that I know about.
她说她没事了  但我知道她肯定没有
She says she's past it, but I know she's not.
从她眼神里能看出来
I can see it in her eyes.
你觉得她是故意以身犯险来自虐吗
You think she's purposely putting herself in harm's way?
我觉得她早已不在乎自己的安危了
I don't think she cares what happens to her either way.
-她现在在哪  -她正要进去
- Where is she now? - She's going in.
我把免提给你打开
I'm going to put you on speaker.
举起手来
Hands up.
转过身去
Turn around.
去吧
Go.
你好吗  瓦德
Hello, Vlad.
蕾妮
Renee.
你整容了
You changed your face.
我在加拉加斯整的
I had it done in Caracas.
你觉得怎样
What do you think?
让你看起来更年轻了
Makes you look younger.
看来你该向我引荐下这位医生
I should get the name of that doctor.
他已经不再行医了
He's not practicing anymore.
真不幸
A sad story.
我们的小朋友说
Our little friend here
你过去一直待在墨西哥城
says you were in Mexico City.
在那干吗
For what?
做点生意而已
Had some business.
不错  我自己在那也有些生意联络人
Good for you. I have some contacts there myself.
我知道你有联络人
Yeah, I know you do.
那么...
So...
报几个名字给我听听吧
give me names.
佩拉塔·罗德里格斯家族...
The Peralta-Rodriguez family....
佩拉塔·罗德里格斯家族
The Peralta-Rodriguez family.
瓜达拉哈拉的卡特雷尼斯
Castorenas in Guadalajara.
我认识拉蒙  他兄弟路易斯
I know Ramon. Is his brother Luiz
还在做他的海洛因买卖吗
still running their heroin operations?
路易斯九个月前被墨西哥联邦警察击毙了
He was killed nine months ago by the Federales.
他九个月前被墨西哥联邦警察击毙了
Not since he was killed by the Federales nine months ago.
蕾妮
You know, Renee,
既然你已经提到了
now that you mention it,
我发现你也似乎有些不一样了
there is something different about you, too.
你指的什么
How do you mean?
你的眼神
Your eyes.
还有皮肤
Your skin.
看起来糟透了
You look like hell.
用枪指着我  脸色怎么好得起来
Well, it's hard to look your best with a gun in your face.
不  我说的不是这个
No, that's not it.
而是别的
Something else.
你生病了吗
Have you been sick?
没有
No.
也许是你在这一路上
Maybe you picked up a little
不小心感染了C型肝炎呢
Hepatitis C on your travels?
在墨西哥城的时候你住哪
Where were you staying in Mexico City?
贝拉酒店
The Bella.
贝拉诺谢酒店
Bella Noche Hotel.
贝拉诺谢酒店  当然
Bella Noche, naturally.
那你肯定该认识那位批准贝拉酒店
Then, of course, you must know the government official who allows it
不受条子干预的政府官员了
to operate without police interference.
克罗伊  墨西哥城的那酒店里
Chloe, the hotel in Mexico City--
有没有一个贪赃枉法的当地政客
was there a local politician on the take?
-我这里没他的记录  -我也没
- I don't have it here. - Neither do I.
-去缉毒局数据库查查  -赶紧
- Checking DEA database. - Come on.
-克罗伊  -给我一分钟
- Chloe. - Give me a minute.
她可没一分钟时间了
She doesn't have a minute.
他叫什么名字
Waiting for a name!
说啊  告诉他
Go ahead, tell him.
我真的厌倦了这种把戏了  瓦德
Really getting tired of this, Vlad.
什么名字
His name!
查到了  是劳尔·卡斯蒂洛
Got it-- Raul Castillo.
卡斯蒂洛  劳尔·卡斯蒂洛
Castillo, Raul Castillo.
劳尔·卡斯蒂洛  满意了吗
Raul Castillo, all right?
玩够你问我答的游戏了吗
Are we done playing 20 questions now?
当然  我觉得是
Yes, I believe we are.
蕾妮  我差点都忘了
You know, Renee, I had almost forgotten
你是多么有趣的一个女人
how much fun you are.
你和其他女人不同
You're not like other women.
你有种
You have balls.
你的嘴还是那么甜
Hmm, you always did say the nicest things.
那现在我们能谈谈这笔买卖了吗
Can we talk about this deal now?
我也希望是这么简单
I wish it were that simple.
把她绑起来
Tie her up.
什么
What?
瓦德  你在干什么
Vlad, what are you doing?
我问的所有问题你全答对了  蕾妮
You gave me all the right answers, Renee,
-但你没说实话  -你犯了一个大错
- but you're not telling the truth. - You're making a mistake.
这次买卖是你千载难逢的机会
This is the chance of a lifetime.
也把他绑起来
Him, too.
瓦德  等等
Vlad, wait.
把他们关进后备箱里
Put them in the trunk.
瓦德米尔  不要这样
Vladimir, Vladimir, no!
瓦德米尔  求你别这么做
No, Vladimir, please don't do this!
听我说
Listen to me!
是她来找我的
She come to me!
是她到我这来的
She come to my place,
那个臭婊子
the bitch!
我发誓
I swear!
瓦德米尔  我一点都不知情
Vladimir, I don't know anything about this!
不
No!
克罗伊  到底怎么了
Chloe, what the hell just happened?
他们把她关进了后备箱  我听不到了
They put her in the trunk, I lost audio.
正在增强信号
Boosting the signal now.
蕾妮
Renee?
再试试
Try it again.
蕾妮  你听得到吗
Renee, can you hear me?
说话
Say something.
克罗伊  还是听不到她
Chloe, I don't have her.
那估计是装甲车
Then the car must be armored.
要么就是她的通讯器短路了
Either that or her comm shorted out.
你看到了吗
Are you seeing this?
看到了
I am.
我正向北追踪  穿过一条小巷到伍德沃德街
Okay, I'm following north through an alley towards Woodward.
我觉得这次行动搞砸了
I think this operation just blew up.
杰克  你准备中途拦截吗
Jack, are you planning to intercept?
如果是装甲车的话不行
Not if the car is armored.
我需要战术支援
I'm gonna need tactical support.
我告诉黑斯廷斯紧急调派一支小队
I'm alerting Hastings to scramble a team now.
告诉他  车里有四个人
Tell him I see four men in the car,
而且要假定  他们是要把蕾妮带到某处灭口
and we're going to have to assume they're taking Renee somewhere to kill her.
-明白  -该死的
- Copy that. - Damn it.
别工作得太晚了  亲爱的
Don't work too late, hon.
你回家的时候打给我
Call me when you're on the road.
我会的
Will do.
莱文医生
Dr. Levine.
你们是怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
我弟弟病了
My brother is sick.
我现在不给病人看病
I'm not seeing patients right now.
他需要医治
He needs your help.
-我给你叫救护车  -不行
- I'm gonna call you an ambulance. - No.
不能让别人知道
No one else can know about this.
我的人都在新罗谢尔你家外面守着
My men are outside your house in New Rochelle.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
我刚和我太太通过电话
I just spoke to my wife.
我们在门外
We're outside the gate.
地址是布鲁克街1614号
The address is 1614 Brook Street.
你女儿房间的灯 十分钟前刚刚熄灭
The light in your little daughter's room just went out about ten minutes ago,
所以我要你把电话放下
so I want you to put the phone down
因为你不会和任何人说这件事
because you're not going to try to warn anybody about this.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我明白
I understand.
我弟弟辐射中毒
My brother has radiation poisoning.
他需要治疗
He needs treatment.
他的症状看起来很严重
His symptoms seem quite advanced.
我不知道我能做什么
I'm not sure what it is I can do for him.
为了你的家人好  你最好赶快医治他
Well, you'd better be able to do something, for your family's sake.
我  我得知道他接触的是何种核物质
I, um... I need to know what kind of materials he came in contact with.
是铀
It was uranium.
你知道是哪种变体吗  哪种同位素
Do you know what variant, the isotope?
武器级别  235
Weapons-grade 235.
杰克  我是黑斯廷斯
Jack, this is Hastings.
战术小队三分钟后赶到
TAC teams are three minutes away.
他们都知道蕾妮在后备箱吗
All of them aware that Renee is in the trunk?
给他们的指令是只听我的号令再出击
The instructions are to engage only on my command.
有迹象表明他们要把她带到哪去吗
Any indication where they're taking her?
-没有  -等他们到达之后再出击可以吗
- None. - Any percentage in letting this play out?
不行  她一从车里出来
No. As soon as she's out of the vehicle,
就会很容易受攻击
she becomes that much more vulnerable.
如果我们现在出击  就意味着任务结束了
If we engage now, it means ending the operation.
任务已经结束了
This operation's over.
瓦德米尔没上钩
Vladimir didn't take the bait.
目标转向南  朝弗拉兴街去了
Target just turned south on Flushing.
杰克  那是一条前方2.6英里处
Jack, that's a feeder onto the BQE
上布鲁克林-皇后区高速公路的岔路
in 2.6 miles.
黑斯廷斯  如果我们不在高速公路下出击
Mr. Hastings, if we don't engage on these surface streets,
我们就失去战术优势了
we lose our tactical advantage.
克罗伊  告诉我截击预计时间
Chloe, get me an ETA.
还有2分10秒
Intercept in... two minutes, ten seconds.
长官  你该打电话了
Sir, you need to make the call now.
好的  我批准截击行动
All right, I'm authorizing engagement.
准备接收截击计划
Stand by for intercept protocols.
这里很好  停车
This is good. Pull over.
打开
Open it.
瓦德米尔  把她们从后备箱拖出来
Vladimir. Take them out of the trunk.
卢戈  求求你  告诉瓦德米尔
Lugo, please, you tell him, tell Vladimir...
克罗伊  又有信号了
Chloe, I've got a signal again.
求求你  瓦德米尔
Please, Vladimir, Vlad...
出问题了  听起来他们停车了
Something's wrong-- they definitely sound stopped,
但我跟踪的车辆还在弗拉兴街向南行驶
but the vehicle I'm following is still going south on Flushing.
-是她叫我来找你的  -闭嘴  兹亚
- She told me to come to you! - Shut up, shut up, Ziya.
这一点用都没有
It's not going to do any good.
你说得对  杰克  目标还在移动
Confirming that, Jack, the target is still moving.
克罗伊  我们跟踪的是个诱饵
Chloe, we're following a decoy.
他们肯定是坐另一辆车离开的  给我找出来
They must have left in another vehicle. Find it!
好  我把卫星画面调出来
Okay, pulling up a satellite footage.
好了  战术小队 原地等待
All right, TAC teams,hold your positions, stand by.
杰克  第一辆驶出汽车零件大楼五分钟后
Jack,another car drove out of the back of the auto parts building
大楼后面又开出了另一辆车
five minutes after the first one.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?!
很抱歉  我们注意力全集中到你跟进的目标了
I'm sorry, we were focusing everything on your follow.
告诉我他们在哪
Just tell me where they are!
把他们带到水边去
Take them down to the water.
好了  我用GPS找到了蕾妮
Okay, I've got a GPS lock on Renee.
他们在新镇河停下了
They're pulled off at Newtown Creek,
就在布莱恩纪念大桥南侧
just south of Bryne Memorial Bridge.
-战术小队在哪  -我正让他们改道
- Where are the TAC teams? - I'm redirecting them now.
他们还有多远
How far out are they?
-至少要十分钟  -让他们赶快
- At least ten minutes. - Tell them to move it.
恢复我和蕾妮的通讯  该死的
Put me back on to Renee's comm. Damn it!
蕾妮  我是杰克
Renee, it's Jack.
我知道你听得见
I know you can hear me.
瓦德米尔引诱我们跟错了目标
Vladimir had us following a decoy.
战术小队还有十分钟能到
TAC teams are ten minutes out.
我现在就赶过来
I'm on my way now.
尽量争取时间
Do whatever you have to to buy time.
你们两个  都跪下
On your knees, both of you.
请听我说  我什么都不知道
Please listen to me, I don't know anything.
闭上嘴
Shut your mouth.
我再给你最后一次机会
I'm going to give you one last chance
告诉我怎么回事
to tell me what is going on.
瓦德米尔  我发誓  是她来找我的
Vladimir, I swear on my life, she come to my place.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything.
不
No!
蕾妮
Renee.
Renee?!
真令人惊讶
Amazing.
你眼都不眨一下
You didn't even blink.
开枪啊
Go ahead.
一了百了
Just get it over with.
蕾妮  你究竟在干什么
Renee, what the hell are you doing?
还不是时候
Not yet.
看在上帝的份上  别让我死得难堪
For God's sake, don't make me grovel.
快他妈开枪吧
Just pull the damn trigger.
那之前我想要知道真相
First I want to hear the truth.
我想知道你到底是谁
I want to know who you really are.
我到底是谁
Who I really am?
是啊  你是谁  别耍花招  蕾妮
Yeah, who you are, not a game, Renee...
或者不管你的名字叫什么
or whatever your name is.
好吧  你想知道真相
Fine, you want the truth?
我就告诉你真相
I'll tell you the truth.
你说得对
You were right.
你说对了  我有病
You were right, I am sick.
我厌倦了这样活着
I am so sick of living like this.
真相就是...
The truth is...
即使你现在放我走
even if you let me walk right now...
我也没处可去  没人投靠
I have nowhere to go and no one to go to.
你不想做这笔买卖
You don't want to do this deal,
可以
fine.
那你还是杀了我吧
Then you might as well just kill me
因为这是我仅有的东西
because this deal is the only thing that I have.
蕾妮  别这样
Renee, please don't do this, please.
再说  凡是你要对我做的事
Besides, you wouldn't be doing anything
我自己已经都一一尝试过了
that I haven't already tried myself.
杀了我吧
Do it.
杀了我
Do it!
开枪啊
Pull the trigger!
我只是需要确定一下
I had to be sure.
你明白的  是吧
You understand, right?
明白
Yes.
好  很好
Good... good.
把他丢进河里去
Dump him in the river.
杰克  战术小队马上就到了
Jack, TAC teams are almost there.
我要知道最新进展
I need a status update.
杰克  你在吗
Jack, are you there?
听到了吗
Do you copy?
告诉战术小队停止行动
You tell the TAC teams to stand down.
怎么了
What's going on?
她混进去了
She's in.
他们相信她了
They bought her cover.